The most special moment is when you take steps
in the right direction towards your dreams
[music]
Or towards a big house
Or towards giving your children their desired career
Or
towards fulfilling your parents' wishes
Celebrate even the small special moments while achieving big dreams
Go on a dream vacation
Upgrade your car for a fabulous romantic trip For every such
moment of happiness, big or small, you need a plan that gives you
both a little for the future and a little for today
Presenting ICICI Pru Goal A
plan that gives you instant income
starting from the first month or year for life and also
a handsome amount on maturity
Life cover for the entire policy term Freedom to accumulate income
or withdraw anytime
Guaranteed booster every 5 years Option to
not take income now and get higher income later
Option to maturity of policy from age 99 ICICI Pru Gold
offers you three plans Delayed Income
with Instant Income Booster
Delayed Income
Start investing with Rs. 1 lakh and at the
age of 99  Maturity is ₹10 lakh. With the accelerated income
option, he will receive an
annual income of ₹37,000 from the first year till the age of 99
at an AR of 8%.
[Music]
If he chooses the circular income with booster plan option,
he will receive an annual income
of ₹37,000 from the first year till the age of 99 at an AR of 8%,
along with a
guaranteed booster payout of ₹12,500 every 5 years.
[Music]
If he wants to save money for the future,
he can choose the deferred income option. For example,
if he wants to receive his income after 11 years,
he will
receive an increased income of ₹12,000 starting from the age of 35 today, till the age of 47 till the age of 99 at an AR of 8%. Not only this,
in each of these plan options, he will also get a majority lakh and
life cover for the entire policy term. This policy
also offers the option to offset the premium by depositing money in the savings wallet. A plan
that understands the needs of today and tomorrow and
gives you  A little for the future and a little
for today With ICICI Pru Gold, make
sure your tomorrow starts today
[Music]